{
    "subject": "resource/Steven_Campbell_(footballer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Australia",
    "human_readable": "Steven Campbell (footballer) was born in Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8933749794960022,
            "question": "Where was Steven Campbell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.807404637336731,
            "question": "When was Steven Campbell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190822720527649,
            "question": "What is Steven Campbell's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6062095761299133,
            "question": "Is Steven Campbell a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6019029021263123,
            "question": "In what country did Steven Campbell play football professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5454352498054504,
            "question": "What teams has Steven Campbell played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5147445797920227,
            "question": "Is Steven Campbell still playing football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4630715548992157,
            "question": "What positions has Steven Campbell played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4508064389228821,
            "question": "What sport is Steven Campbell known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3376040756702423,
            "question": "Has Steven Campbell won any major awards in his football career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steven Campbell (footballer) was born in Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6228_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport is Steven Campbell known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6228_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What positions has Steven Campbell played?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6228_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Steven Campbell still playing football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6228_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6228_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not support the statement that Steven Campbell (footballer) was born in Australia. According to the provided context, Steven Campbell was born on August 20, 1986, in Kirkcaldy, Fife, Scotland, and played for clubs in Perth, Western Australia, but there is no information indicating he was born there."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Steven Campbell (footballer) was born in Perth, Western Australia but as context states he was born on August 20, 1986 in Kirkcaldy, Fife, Scotland.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from context 2 & 3 states he was born in Perth, Western Australia.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information (1) states that Steven Campbell (footballer) was born on August 20, 1986, in Kirkcaldy, Scotland.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}